Let me try an appeal.
oh
Which one?
uh
I'd like to go to Wausan
no
Let’s try it with a broadcasting station.
broadcasting station
I'll do it now
Shouldn’t it be done with a jangdel?
I need to appeal with a jangdelai.
Oh yes that's right
All right
page
Jandel has arrived
field
We are looking for people who will listen
let
But it went well
It was okay
I hope it's okay
Oh, it's like this.
Oh it was okay
Oh okay
It was okay
Let's go like this
Me too, a little bit like this
are you okay?
I will go after testing the microphone.
My brother, who spent 30,000 won earlier.
Thank you so much.
sure.
A feeling of gratitude.
I will try to appeal.
Thank you, brother.
thank you
uh?
But the piano doesn't play.
The piano doesn't play.
I was planning to go right in.
What should I do?
Now, here we get minus 20 points.
Since I'm sick right now, there's a fuss about the TV.
TV because it hurts.
There is no piano sound.
No, it's too embarrassing.
Hey, thank you.
I picked one.
Nothing in this world goes your way, right?
No, really, this is humanity’s first broadcasting station.
Hey, thank you.
It's because I'm so grateful.
Just don't look at it for a moment.
hi.
Goodbye if you smile.
If you just live a busy life
I thought it would be easily forgotten.
It wasn't easy.
It came to mind.
Every time I see a gait that resembles yours
Every time I see someone who looks like you
I have no choice but to look back
It has no choice but to be like that
I'll have lunch. I'll have lunch.
with me
I'm sorry, I'm crazy
It's my selfish greed until the end
I hope you're happy
I hope you are happy
hi
Why do you try to brighten the ending too?
Thank you.
I do, I do
Good quality of the song
I thought I was at a jazz bar
It's crazy now
I'm in big trouble
I'm a fan of sandalwood, and thunder lily is number one.
What should I do?
I'll give you the door
I am also a fan of Deulle, but Thunder Lily is the winner.
But really
Oh my real music
But really, how do you sing so well?
Right now, among the Choi clans, I was the best singer.
You speak English really well. Is it your native language?
He says, please talk to me.
It's not my native language
I really liked English
I lived there briefly when I was young.
But even after that, I really liked English.
music
Because I like English songs
Because I like pop songs
Because I kept calling it that a lot.
It seems natural
Well, the people out there
oh, they look so fast and alive
as far as I'm concerned
it's not all about do or die
Still, I lace my shoes
I go for a run
I've got to move on
though it's hard to be done
at the end of the day
the subtle delays
or give it a break
it will never matter to me
at the end of the day
ah
Please announce only 1st place
1st place
ruler
It's 361 points.
first
broadcast
1st place
Luca Maina
ah
Thank you guys
This is so
I'm so honored to be here
Thank you guys
Really
I love you
Korean language too
If I do it again
hello
I really really really appreciate it.
everyone
hello
Stop it, you really
uh
How are you feeling?