👸 Hwa-jin: I think it was around
New Year last year,
👸 Hwa-jin: A coworker and I said,
Let us try something new,
👸 Hwa-jin: so we planned a hike.
👸 Hwa-jin: To Achasan, probably
the easiest mountain in Seoul.
👸 Hwa-jin: Wait, why are you laughing?
🚶🏼‍♀️ Jin-young: It just made me think of
a subway stop.
👸 Hwa-jin: Exactly.
👸 Hwa-jin: It is actually a pretty
manageable mountain
👸 Hwa-jin: for someone like me.
👸 Hwa-jin: Achasan. That Achasan.
👸 Hwa-jin: And there is tteokbokki
at the bottom.
👸 Hwa-jin: That was the best
I could do.
🤦🏻‍♀️ A-sol: So how was it,
once you got up there?
👸 Hwa-jin: I thought,
Oh, this is doable,
👸 Hwa-jin: which, of course,
makes sense.
👸 Hwa-jin: I picked an easy mountain
on purpose.
🚶🏼‍♀️ Jin-young: I do not think I have ever been
🚶🏼‍♀️ Jin-young: to any mountain
other than Namsan.
🤦🏻‍♀️ A-sol: Then please remain silent.
🤦🏻‍♀️ A-sol: You do not qualify.
🤦🏻‍♀️ A-sol: You laughed the second
you heard "Achasan,"
🤦🏻‍♀️ A-sol: and I thought you were naming
some epic mountain.