Wow, Song Ah-cheol and Jeong Ji-soo
It was a smile. and.
It's crazy.
>> It's so good.
No, everyone else is like this too
While listening, the room becomes your own space.
You also said things have changed.
>> uh and now that it's over
I'm going up and listening to all the music.
There was. Everyone stay still.
>> Right.
>> Hey, but thank you so much.
You can hear this performance in space.
I guess.
>>Thank you for having us.
>> Ah, humility again.
But I really think this is a child’s agenda
As someone who doesn't know much about
I want to ask you something
>> Watching the performance, now in the middle of the solo
Now applaud when you do this or this
You hit it.
>> These people actually know a lot about ashes
If not, when should I hit it? a little
There are people who don't know this.
How do you know that?
>> Usually you have to count the number of words.
no?
>> What are you doing when you come here to do it?
Or what do you do? commonly
now
>> yes
>> The melody is usually roughly preceded by a verse.
Melody and yes
>> then
>> Someone keep playing like this first
You say it.
>> And when you move on to someone else
>> You can applaud at that time.