>> That thing is a bit off.
>> Ah, but you have to show off as the owner.
Does it work?
>> That's what I think these days.
>> It's just that if you don't like me, you don't like me.
>> Hmm. hmm.
>> When I used that gun at that club
>> That scene that Yunju saw, that scene
>> Ha-cheol’s expression when he shot
>> Yes.
>> His eyes were completely scary, but he was smiling
There was. So that person is usually
no. I was thinking about it mentally.
>> I was smiling.
>> Yes.
Oh, that's right
>> The eyes are
>> Smiling like a psychopath, this kind of thing
It wasn't
>> I was laughing but I was shedding tears
no? It's not like that. a little
>> When you blow on the instrument, the lip rises
Something like that
>> No, no, take out the instrument and now next to it.
When I was standing like this, it was a bit real
These guys are fun, I just feel like this
You have a leisurely smile. So uh
I will be mentally strong.
>> Oh, it's strong. I'm mentally strong.
>> Because I have experienced a lot in that area.
I think I've gotten stronger.
>> That's also a bit upsetting. however
He wasn't a strong person from the beginning
That's right. yes.
>> That's right. I learned a lot from all of that.
I think so.
>> How should I deal with it and what should I do?
I get hurt less
>> Now, as time goes by, these things
>> Uh ah really please just do the basics
Let’s live while protecting it. We really are then